Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Miscellaneous TDF Information, 1979 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1978-1979 Programs, July 1979 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1977-1978 Programs, July 1978 (Box 71)
  - Charles Reinhart Board Meeting, Apr. 21, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund, June 1, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund Board Meeting, Sept. 13, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund Board of Directors Policy Meeting, Apr. 26, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1976-1977 Programs, Aug. 1977 (Box 71)
  - Charles Reinhart Board Meeting, Nov. 16, 1977 (Box 71)
  - National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts, 1983 (Box 71)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program Requirements of the Office of National Coordinator, July 1971 (Box 71)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Correspondence and Grant Applications, 1966-1971 (Box 71)
  - Taylor Summer Tour General Info, 1966 (Box 71)
  - McKayle (Box 71)
  - Alex Katz (Box 71)
  - Office for Artistic Tours and Shows in the R.P.R. (Romania) Printed Materials (Box 71)
  - Vikings (Box 71)
  - Julie and Jack (Box 71)
  - Ted Williams (Box 71)
  - Lucas Hoving (Box 71)
  - Lucas Hoving (Box 71)
  - Netherlands Chamber Orchestra (Box 71)
  - Cologne, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Belgium TV, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Edinburgh (Box 71)
  - Edinburgh (Box 71)
  - Israel (Box 71)
  - Holland Festival, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Connecticut Commissions on the Arts, 1968 (Box 71)
  - CRMI Financial Taxes 1985 (Box 71)
  - CRMI Office Handbook (Box 71)
  - Workshop Materials for Jean Danser (Box 71)
  - AIS Support Staff (Box 71)
  - AIS General Information (Box 71)
  - AIS Equipment (Box 71)
  - AIS Equipment (Box 71)
  - AIS, 1980 (Box 72)
  - AIS Printing (Box 72)
  - AIS Hospitality (Box 72)
  - AIS Accounting (Box 72)
  - AIS Forms (Box 72)
  - AIS Workshop Space, Equipment, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIE Post Workshop Clean-Up (Box 72)
  - AIS Workshop Parties, Breaks, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIE Workshop VIPS, 1981 (Box 72)
  - CR Introduction (Box 72)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Artists Kit Materials, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIS Workshop Group Leaders, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIS Workshop Workforce, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIS Workshop Space, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIS Artists Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous AIE Workshop, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Legal Requirements for NEA Support for Dance Companies (Box 72)
  - AIE Announcements (Box 72)
  - AIE Workshop New Artists Orientation, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Kit Materials, 1981 (Box 72)
  - AIS/Dance Component Calendars: Chron/Artist/State, 1980-1981 (Box 72)
  - Requests for Assistants, 1980-1981 (Box 72)
  - Taylor's Follies (Film), 1975 (Box 72)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Printed Materials, 1964-1967 (Box 72)
  - Artists Management, 1964-1969 (Box 72)
  - Paul Taylor Press (and Translations from Italian), 1963-1967 (Box 72)
  - Glen Tetley at Vancouver Festival, 1967 (Box 72)
  - NEA Media Project (Replace Blue Book) (Box 72)
  - Handbook Comments, L. Shapiro Copy (Box 72)
  - AIS/DC Handbook, L. Shapiro Project Replaces G. Wenner's Handbook (Box 72)
  - NEA Media Project Replacement for Blue Book (Box 72)
  - "Move!" Preparation (Box 72)
  - Dancing in the Schools Condensed, 1978 (Box 72)
  - Dancing in the Schools Photographs (Box 72)
  - Distribution of Dancing in the Schools (Box 72)
  - Dance in the Schools Office Copies (Box 72)
  - Dance in the Schools AIS/DC Handbook Preparation (Box 72)
  - Dance in the Schools Reprint (Box 72)
  - Dance in the Schools Update, 1976 (Box 72)
  - "Move!" Distribution (Box 72)
  - "Move!" Distribution File AIS/DC Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 72)
  - Dance in the Schools Distribution 1975-1976 (Box 72)
  - "Dancers in Schools" Film (Box 72)
  - "Reaching" (Box 72)
  - "Reaching" Distribution File AIS/DC Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 72)
  - "Reaching" Distribution File AIS/DC Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 72)
  - AIS/DC Calendar, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - Calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - AIS/DC Calendar, 1974-1975 (Box 73)
  - AIS/DC Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 73)
  - NEA AIS/DC Guidelines, 1978-1979 (Box 73)
  - AIS/DC Guidelines NEA Proposed Changes, 1978-1979 (Box 73)
  - NEA AIS/DC Guidelines, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - NEA AIS/DC Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 73)
  - NEA AIS/DC Guidelines, 1975-1976 (Box 73)
  - Don Redlich Dance Company Accounting, 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Lucas Hoving Dance Company Accounting, 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Accounting, 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Accounting, 1969 (Box 73)
  - Accounting, 1967-1971 (Box 73)
  - Lucas Hoving Accounting, 1969 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Accounting, 1966-1967 (Box 73)
  - Glen Tetley Accounting, 1969 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Program Typescripts, 1962-1966 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Clippings, 1960-1962 (Box 73)
  - Don Redlich Tour Accounting, 1967-1969 (Box 73)
  - Glen Tetley Tour Accounting, 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Accounting, 1968 (Box 73)
  - Donald McKayle Tour Accounting, 1969-1970 (Box 73)
  - Letters to Colleges, 1961-1964 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor European Correspondence, 1962 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Brochure, 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor October Tour, Oct. 1965 (Box 73)
  - Customs 1963 Mexico Taylor Closed, 1966 (Box 73)
  - Billy Rose Playbill Proofs Taylor, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor, Bangkok, Thailand, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Asia, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor Asian Tour, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Mata and Hari (Box 73)
  - Reine Flachot (Box 73)
  - Anne Wilson (Box 73)
  - Yuriko (Box 73)
  - Carlos de la Camara (Box 73)
  - George Stam (Box 73)
  - Paul Taylor, Korea, Okinawa, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Ted Shawn, 1961 (Box 73)
  - Ted Shawn, 1961 (Box 73)
  - Summer Workshop AIS Job Alikes, Cross Jobs, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Agenda, Schedules, etc., 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Architecture Meeting, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Artists' Policy Meeting, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Comments, Suggestions, Evaluations, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Confirmation Letters, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Housing, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Information Requests, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Tom Bergin's Speech (Cong.), 1976 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Resolutions, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - CR's Comments on Resolutions (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Handicapped, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop State Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Complete Folder, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Originals (Dynacopy), 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Press, Programs, etc., 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - Notices to ADF re: Summer Workshop Arrangements, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Artists' Policy Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Group Leaders, Presenters, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Thank You Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Speakers, Group Leaders, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Resource Handbook for SAA Coordinator, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 74)
  - Summer Workshop Agendas, 1977 (Box 74)
  - Summer Workshop Room Reservation Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 74)
  - AIS Dance Component Memos to SAAs and Artists, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Alabama (Box 74)
  - Alabama, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Arizona, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Arizona (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls California (Box 74)
  - California, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Connecticut (Box 74)
  - Connecticut, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Delaware (Box 74)
  - Delaware, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Florida (Box 74)
  - Florida, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Hawaii, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Hawaii (Box 74)
  - Hawaii, 1979-1980 (Box 74)
  - Illinois, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Illinois (Box 74)
  - Indiana, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Indiana (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Iowa (Box 74)
  - Kentucky, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Kentucky (Box 74)
  - Louisiana, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Louisiana, 1978-1979 (Box 74)
  - Phone Calls Louisiana (Box 75)
  - Maine, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Maine (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Massachusetts (Box 75)
  - Massachusetts, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Michigan, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Michigan (Box 75)
  - Missouri, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Missouri (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Montana (Box 75)
  - Nevada, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Nevada (Box 75)
  - New Hampshire, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls New Hampshire (Box 75)
  - New Jersey, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls New Jersey (Box 75)
  - New Mexico, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls New Mexico (Box 75)
  - Iowa, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - New York, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls New York (Box 75)
  - North Carolina, 1979 (Box 75)
  - North Dakota, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls North Dakota (Box 75)
  - Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Ohio (Box 75)
  - Oregon, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Oregon (Box 75)
  - Pennsylvania, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Pennsylvania (Box 75)
  - Puerto Rico, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Puerto Rico (Box 75)
  - Rhode Island, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Rhode Island (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Tennessee (Box 75)
  - Tennessee, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Utah, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Utah (Box 75)
  - Virgin Islands, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Virgin Islands (Box 75)
  - Washington, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Washington (Box 75)
  - Phone Calls Wisconsin (Box 75)
  - Non_Participating States (Box 75)
  - Non_Participating States (Box 75)
  - Coordinator Info Sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 76)
  - AIS/DC Directory Originals, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - AIS Directory Office File Copies, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Program Information (Box 76)
  - Notes re: AIS Directory and Program Information, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - AIS/DC Dance Company Information not in 1979-1980 Directory (Box 76)
  - AIS/DC Memos Sent with Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - AIS/DC Directory Mailings and Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Supplemental Directory Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Memos Sent with Supplement to DMS, DC, and States, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Supplement to the Directory File Copies, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
  - Directory Table of Contents All Years (Box 76)
  - Dance Co. and DMS Directory Sheet and Instructions, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Directory Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Company Biographies (Box 76)
  - DMS/DC Information and Resumes not Included in 1980-1981 Directory (Box 76)
  - AIS Directory Program Information Memos Accompanying Mailing, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - AIS Directory Distribution, Printing Estimates Info, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Program Information Originals, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Distribution and Printing Info Directory, Abbreviated Directory, and Supplement, 1979-1981 (Box 76)
  - Memos Sent with Supplement to SAA, New DMS, New DC, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - AIS Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Supplement to the Directory File Copies, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Directory Xeroxes with Corrections, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Directory Sheets Applications Rejected, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Directory Sheet Log, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Applicants' Directory Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
  - Sampler Program Information Memos Sent, 1981-1982 (Box 76)
  - Sampler Program Information Originals and Copies, 1981-1982 (Box 76)
  - Sampler Program Info (Box 76)
  - AIE Program Information, 1981-1982 (Box 76)
  - Massachusetts Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Michigan Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Schedules Redlich, Hoving, Taylor, Limon, Nikolais, ABT, 1969-1970 (Box 76)
  - Mitchell-Harlem SUNY-NYS, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Don Redlich NYSCA Application (Box 76)
  - Betty Jones SUNY-NYS, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - SUNY-NYS State Sponsors, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Lucas Hoving NYSCA Application, 1970 (Box 76)
  - Hoving Taxes and Budget, 1968 (Box 76)
  - Paul Taylor NYSCA Application (Box 76)
  - New York State SUNY Touring Program, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Murray Louis SUNY-NYS, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Martha Graham SUNY-NYS, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Martha Graham SUNY-NYS, 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - CRMI General Ledger, ADF Income Statements, 1982 (Box 77)
  - AIE Workshop, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Final Report (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1970-1971 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1971-1972 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1972-1973 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1973-1974 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1974-1975 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1975-1976 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1976-1977 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - AIS Dance Component Final Report, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - AIS Final Reports All Years and Other Statistics (Box 77)
  - NEA CA 80-4 AIS Contract Final Report, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - NEA Contract AIS/Dance Component, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - NEA AIS Dance Component Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - AIS Contract NEA CA 80-4 Amendment #2, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - AIS NEA Contract # NEA CA 80-4 Amendment #1, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - AIS Contract NEA PC 81-12 Negotiated Contract, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
  - NEA PC 79-5 Contract AIS, July 1, 1978-Sept. 30, 1979 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Board Meeting Minutes (Box 77)
  - Congress and the Contract (Box 77)
  - AIS/DC Endowment Contract Miscellaneous Correspondence, Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - Contract General Correspondence with NEA Important Issues (Box 77)
  - AIS Contract Budget Estimate, Worksheets, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - AIS Contract Background, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - NEA AIS Contract Budget and Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Form 990 and Schedule A, 1983 (Box 77)
  - NEA Grant No. 92-3524-074 (Crowsnest) Senehan, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - John Mark Rudkin Charitable Foundation Contribution to Senehan, Mar. 12, 1980 (Box 77)
  - Lee Lichter (Box 77)
  - Senehan Chart of Accounts (Box 77)
  - ADP Senehan (Box 77)
  - ADP Senehan, July 1979-June 1980 (Box 77)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - Senehan ADP, June 30, 1981 (Box 77)
  - General Financial AIS History (Box 77)
  - Senehan File 020091 12.4 (Box 77)
  - DMS Payment Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - AIS, 1973-1974 (Box 77)
  - AIS, 1972-1973 (Box 77)
  - Revised AIS Grant Reports (Box 77)
  - Old AIS Worksheets re: Surplus (Box 77)
  - DMS Payment Schedule, 1979 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Analysis of Financial Activity, July 1, 1978-June 30, 1979 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Analysis of Financial Activity, July 1, 1977-June 30, 1978 (Box 77)
  - Senehan Computer (Box 77)
  - Senehan ADP (Box 77)
  - Senehan Tax File 12.1 (Box 77)
  - AIS Calendar, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Site Meetings (Box 77)
  - AIS Group Leaders Suggestions for Discussion, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Reimbursement Form, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS General Conference Information, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Participants List, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Agenda, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Complete Packet, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Memo to Participants, May 27, 1977 (Box 77)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Letters to Superintendents from CR, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop NEA Correspondence re: SW, 1977-1978 (Box 77)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Evaluations, 1977 (Box 77)
  - AIS Summer Workshop "Go Through for Planning Meeting", 1977 (Box 77)
  - Artists Advisory Committee Questionnaire for Summer Workshop, 1977 (Box 77)
  - Artists Advisory Committee Questionnaire for Summer Workshop, 1977 (Box 77)
  - AIS Workshop Planning Meeting, Mar. 28, 1977 (Box 78)
  - AIS/DC Summer Workshop Agenda Comments from Planning Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
  - Senehan General Ledger, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - Senehan Analysis of Financial Activity, July 1, 1974-June 30, 1975 (Box 78)
  - Senehan General Ledger, 1974-1975 (Box 78)
  - Senehan 1099s, 1979 (Box 78)
  - Senehan 1099s, 1978 (Box 78)
  - Senehan 1099s, 1980 (Box 78)
  - DMS Payment Schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
  - Senehan Analysis of Financial Activity, July 1, 1975-June 30, 1976 (Box 78)
  - Bills Which Could Be Charged to AIS (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Contract (Correspondence and Telephone Calls) re: Amendment #1 and #2, 1978-1979 (Box 78)
  - Gades (Box 78)
  - Bicentennial Celebration, 1973-1976 (Box 78)
  - Asia Society for the Performing Arts (Box 78)
  - CR/CRMI Correspondence, 1976 (Box 78)
  - CR/CRMI Correspondence, 1977 (Box 78)
  - Don Redlich Booklet (Box 78)
  - Perlo, Carla, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Peters, Patricia, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Ramirez, Tina, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Rivin, Ruth, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Rose, Phyllis, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Sachs, Susan, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Scott, Judith, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Ruff, Bob, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Smith, Therrell C., 1974 (Box 78)
  - Taylor, Meredith M., 1974 (Box 78)
  - Thuesen, Barbara W., 1974 (Box 78)
  - Townsend, Kathryn, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Winber, Gloria, 1974 (Box 78)
  - Wodynski, Jan, 1974 (Box 78)
  - AIS Chronological File Correspondence, Jan. 1, 1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS NEA Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Expenses Travel Reimbursement, 1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Expenses, 1980 (Box 78)
  - CR Washington DC, Apr. 11, 1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Workshop Expenses, 1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Workshop Expenses, Observer Fees, Tickets, Refunds, 1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Thank You Notes, 1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS State Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS Educators Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Memos to State Arts Agencies, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Memos to the Artists, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS Final Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS Grant Revised Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - DMS Payment Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Log Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIE Guidelines Discussion, Mar. 3, 1981 (Box 78)
  - AIE Panel Meeting, Mar. 12-14, 1981 (Box 78)
  - DTP Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 78)
  - Artists Advisory Committee Memos sent by CRMI, Invoices, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - National Coordination, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Payment Schedule for DMS, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - DMS Payment Exceptions for Fees and Travel, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - AIS Chronological File Correspondence, Oct. 1, 1980-Dec. 31, 1980 (Box 78)
  - Funding Priorities, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - Payment Info and Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Calendars, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - AIS/Dance Component Calendars, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - Assistants, 1980-1981 (Box 79)
  - Response to Announcement Re: Changes in AIS Program (Box 79)
  - AIS General Procedural Information about AIE (Box 79)
  - Photos AIS Program (Box 79)
  - Unused FYI Materials, All Years (Box 79)
  - Contracts: NEA Copies (Box 79)
  - AIS Publicity, Dance and other Components (Box 79)
  - Joyce Dapper (Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous AIS Files (Box 79)
  - SD Action! (Box 79)
  - AIS Last Reports, etc. (Box 79)
  - Contracts: File Copies (Box 79)
  - Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Corporate Records (Box 79)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Artists in Schools booklet (Box 79)
  - Arts in Education Partners: Schools and their Communities, 1977 (Box 79)
  - The Artist in the School: A Report on the Artist-in-residence Project, 1970 (Box 79)
  - Artists in Schools Profile: Dance in Orange, California, June 1, 1975 (Box 79)
  - All the Arts for Every Child, 1975 (Box 79)
  - All the Arts for Every Child, 1975 (Box 79)
  - All the Arts for Every Child, 1975 (Box 79)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company, Music Academy Auditorium, Jan. 28-29, 1967 (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company (5 copies), July 27-30, 1966 (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Breakrules Streb (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Alvin Ailey, American Dance Theater (2 copies) (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company, National Theatre (Box OS1)
  - Don Redlich Dance Company Brochure (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Don Redlich Dance Company, Marymount Manhattan Theatre (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company, Theatre des Champs-Elysees (10 copies) (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Paul Taylor Dance Company, Irvine Auditorium, Nov. 11, 1967 (Box OS1)
  - City Center American Dance Marathon Ticket Brochure, 1972 (Box OS1)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Light Plots (2 folders) (Box OS1)
  - Poster: Ravi Shankar (Box OS1)
  - New York Times Magazine, July 28, 1968 (Box OS1)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Booklet (3 copies) (Box OS1)